Guide to the Historic Photograph Subject File circa 19th century-20th century
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 23: Transportation
  - Brick pavement near Seattle, 1921, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Wallowa Highway, eastern Oregon, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Snoqualmie Pass, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Pacific Hwy east of Olympia, 1919, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Paving road north of Colfax, 1921, 4 items (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Roads around Pullman, 18 items (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Eastern WA road construction, c 1920s and 1930s, 21 item (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Eastern WA road construction, c 1920s and 1930s, 8 items (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Paving road south of Rosalia, 2 items (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Early map of Evergreen Highway, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Construction of US Hwy 10 east of Spokane, 7 items (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Hope/Princeton Highway, Canada, 5 items (Box 35, Folder 18.1)
  - Lolo Indian Trail, 10 items (Box 35, Folder 18.2)
  - Roads from Louisiana, S. Carolina, Mississippi, and Illinois, 4 items (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Spokane and Inland Railroads, 5 items (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Passenger train interior, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Cougar Special at N.P.R.R., Pullman, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Train wreck, Pullman, c. 1892, 2 items (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Inland Empire Railroad system, Garfield, WA, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - First passenger train to Grangeville, ID 1908, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Train scenes, eastern WA and ID, 7 items (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Train wreck scenes, eastern WA, 6 items (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Coeur D'Alene Railway and Navigation Co., 2 items (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - First Great Northern passenger train at Omak, WA 1913, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Old train engine, Stanwood, WA, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Northern pacific passenger trains, 2 items (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Empire Builder railroad, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 31.1)
  - Northern Pacific R.R. views from around the country, 8 items (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Rotary snowplow on Northern Pacific R.R., 1 item (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Canyon Creek railroad, 4 items (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Train engine manufacturing, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - WW II train and tank, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Idaho and WA R.R., 2 items (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Northern Pacific R.R. engine, 1 item (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - White Pass and Yukon Rt. photograph and souvenir deck of cards, 2 items (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Photos of interlocking signal switches, 27 items (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Boeing Flying Fortress (XB-15), 1 item (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Boeing Flying Fortress (B-17B), 1 item (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Boeing B17B, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Boeing plant no. 2, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Boeing 307 Stratoliners, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Boeing 307 Stratoliner, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Boeing 314 PanAmerican Clipper, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Boeing Field c. 1937, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Boeing assembly floor, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Lockheed S-14 of the "Viking Fleet", 1 item (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Wreckage of Wiley Post's airplane, Aug. 17, 1935, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Airmail plane, Fairbanks, AK, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Early airplanes, 5 items (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - First airmail out of Pasco, April 6, 1926, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Richfield Gasoline - Charles Rosner WW2 plane illustrations (trading cards), 1939, 4 items (Box 36, Folder 15.5)
  - U.S. Army tank, July 4, 1949, Tokyo, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Series 24: Wildlife
  - King Salmon, Puget Sound, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Blackfish, Puget Sound, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Man fishing, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Fish catches, 3 items (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - San Juan Fish Co., Seattle, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Frogs, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Catch of pheasant, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Quail, pheasant, and grouse, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Wild ducks, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Feeding ducks at Griffith Hot Springs, c. 1935, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Elk herd near Olympic Hot Springs, c. 1921, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Deer, 8 items (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - "Hunters Bag of Deer", 5 items (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Deer hunting, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Deer pelts, 1932, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Elk, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Bison, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 32.1)
  - Black bears, 6 items (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Bear shots, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Black bears, Mt. Rainier Nat'l Park, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Black bear and cubs, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Bobcat, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - "Charlie" the Disney cougar, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Dead coyote and lynx, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Beaver, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Antelope, 2 items (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Mountain goats, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Female goat at Lake Chelan, 1937, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Wildlife Preserve, Dayton, WA, 1 item (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Rattlesnakes, 9 items (Box 36, Folder 45)
- Series 25: Works Progress Administration (WPA)
  - Federal Writers Project, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Fed. Writers Project, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Fed. Writers Project- American Guide, 5 items (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Fed. Writers exhibit- New York Times Nat'l Book Fair, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Fed. Writers Project- publications, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Fed. Writers project- offices, 1936, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Marine Hospital, Seattle, 1937, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Griffith Hot Springs, 5 items (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - C.C.C. Construction, Sauk River, WA, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Ski hut near Leavenworth, WA, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Frenchtown cross, c. 1935 (Walla Walla), 1 item (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Fort Borst Blockhouse c. 1936, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Fort Simcoe Blockhouse, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Footbridge at Tumwater park, Olympia, c. 1935, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Canal and tunnel, Klamath project, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge, Washington, D.C., 1 item (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Story Gorge Dam, OR, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Nelson's dairies, Jeffersonville, PA, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Ohio Valley Dairy, New Concord, OH, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Aquidneck Island Creamery, Newport, RI, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Schwab Dairy, Peoria, IL, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Rhododendrons, WA state flower, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Stringing overhead trellises for hops, WA, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Wilkerson Miners, Wilkerson, WA, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Women making quilts- panorama, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Women sewing, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Women sewing, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Women sewing, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Women sewing, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Women ironing clothes, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Shoe factory, Seattle, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Shoe repair shop, Seattle, 3 items (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - State and Territorial Seals, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Early map of Mt. Rainier Nat'l Park, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - North America- copy of 1835 statistical map, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Cartoons of Sam Armstrong, 4 items (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Cartoon by "Tige" Reynolds, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - American Newspaper Guild strike leaders, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Wooden Ramage hand press, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Photo of "The Columbian", Sept 11, 1852, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - "Spokesman review", Feb 20,1937, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - "The Evergreen", Nov 15, 1899, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - "College Record" (WSC), Nov. 1892, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - "Auburn Globe-Republican", 1937, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Tacoma "Daily Ledger", 1912, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - "The Aberdeen Daily World", Feb 19, 1937, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Spokane Falls "Evening Chronicle", Sept 21, 1886, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - "Spokane Falls Review", May 19, 1883, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - "The Intelligencer" Building- drawing, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - List of American Guide photos illustrating journalism, 1 item (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - C.C.C. Camp Walla Walla, WA, 1936, 2 items (Box 37, Folder 51)